How do we turn this off? Mom, you think
you can help me turn this off?
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
How do we turn this off?
Can you help me with this?
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
I didn't mean to snap.
Good morning. Many of you
are halfway through...
your first week here at Greendale
and as your dean...
I thought I would share a few thoughts
of wisdom and inspiration.
What is community college?
Well, you've heard all kinds of things.
You've heard it's loser college
for remedial teens...
20-something dropouts,
middle-age divorcees...
and old people keeping their minds active
as they circle the drain of eternity.
That's what you heard.
However, I wish you luck!
Okay, you know-- Uh-oh.
Okay, there's more to this speech.
There's actually a middle card
that is missing.
Can we all look around our immediate areas,
'cause I really wanted to--
I'm only half-Arabic, actually.
My dad is Palestinian.
He's a U.S. citizen. He's not a threat
to national security or anything.
A lot of people want to know that after they
meet him, because he has an angry energy.
But not, like, angry at America.
Just angry at my mom for leaving him.
Although she did leave because he was angry
and he was angry because she's American.
My name's Abed, by the way.
Abed, nice to know you
and then meet you in that order.
- Now about that question that I had--
- Oh, uh...
5 after 11:00 when you asked.
- Abed?
- Yeah?
What's the deal with the hot girl
from Spanish class?
I can't find a road in there.
Well, I only talked to her once
while she was borrowing a pencil, but...
her name is Britta, she's 28,
birthday in October...
she has two older brothers and one of 'em
works with children who have a disorder...
I might want to look up.
Oh, and she thinks she's gonna flunk
tomorrow's test, so she really needs to focus...
so she's sorry
if that makes her seem cold.
Holy crap. Abed...
I see your value now.
That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Absolutely not.
These guys knew you like I did,
they would have given you a small office.
Jeff Winger!
Genius at law.
- You got to stop saying that.
- I will never do that. Sit down.
I still cannot figure out
how you got a jury...
to connect September the 11th with my DUI,
let alone why that helped.
Well, 2002 was a simpler time.
So what is my lawyer doing here?
I'm a student.
Well, that cannot be
an inspiring journey.
Uh, I am in a bit of a jam.
The state bar has
suspended my license.
They found out my college degree
was less than legitimate.
I thought you had a bachelor's
from Columbia.
Now I have to get one from America.
And it can't be an email attachment.
Well, you've picked a fine school.
Yes, and I'm hoping
that our friendship...
will yield certain advantages.
- You know, academic guidance...
- Yes.
...moral support,
every answer to every test...
for every one of the classes
that I'm taking. Here's my schedule.
No. Now, Jeff,
just by asking that...
you have insulted the integrity
of this entire institution.
Oi! Waster!
Not a bathroom!
- Not a bathroom.
- Okay.
Duncan, you did seem less
into integrity...
the day that I convinced
12 of yours peers...
that when you made
that u-turn on the freeway...
and tried to order chalupas
from the emergency call box...
that your only real crime
was loving America.
Well, I do love America.
I love it very much.
Mmm?
I-- I love chalupas.
But?
- I'll look into it.
- Thank you.
Duncan, you are a good man.
Jeff, are you familiar with the adage,
"Cheaters never prosper"?
No, and if I wanted
to learn something...
I wouldn't have come
to community college.
:::   Timecodes  -  gius   :::
- Oh, hey! Spanish.
- Uh, don't hit on me, okay?
Whoa.
I wouldn't dream of it.
I just wanted to let you know
about my Spanish study group.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
The guy who's playing bejeweled
on his iPhone all class has a study group?
Um, can I sign up twice?
I'm taking the class as an easy credit.
I'm actually a Spanish tutor.
- Board certified.
- Can you say that in Spanish now?
- I really need help with Spanish.
- Yeah, I was willing to bet. I'm Jeff...
or Jefe.
- The group meets at the library at 4:00.
- Britta. Thanks.
You're gonna be there?
Poquito mas.
That means, "see you there".
Shouldn't be too hard
to fake a study group, right?
Oh, geez, I'm sorry.
I was raised on TV
and I was conditioned to believe...
that every black woman over 50
is a cosmic mentor.
Were you conditioned to pay
for your damn tacos, Sein-field?
Yes, I'm so sorry.
It's Seinfeld.
Bien-- Bien--
Bienvenido.
"Bienvenuto"!
Hey, all right, come on in.
Uh, got the whole table.
Welcome.
- Yeah, got the whole room.
- Yeah, here's the, uh...
contact sheet.
Just put your stuff there.
Man.
Rest of the group is running late.
But you and I can get acquainted.
You may have noticed this morning,
not so good at the small talk.
- Yeah, I like big talk. What's your deal?
- That's not small talk?
What's your deal
and is God dead?
All right, you want to know my deal?
I dropped out of high school
because I thought...
for some reason
it would impress Radiohead.
You'd be surprised
what gets back to these guys.
I, um-- I joined the Peace Corps.
Did a little foot modeling.
I got tear gassed
at a world trade rally.
Marry me.
And I guess, Jeff, my deal is,
above all else, honesty.
- Honesty?
- Yeah.
You tell me the truth, I will like you.
You lie to me, I will never talk to you again.
- That's my deal.
- Ah, that's a good deal.
- So what's your deal?
- Uh, I would have to go--
I would have to say,
um, honesty...
because...
I would say anything to get what I want
and I want you to like me.
So, uh--
Wow.
That's a very honest answer.
All right, now I like you fine.
Really? Wow.
You're easy.
Hell yeah.
Abed in the house!
- Whoo!
- Whoo. Why?
- Britta invited me. Is that cool?
Oh, I can't think of a single
logical reason why not.
- Cool.
- There you go.
Oh, hey, here. Put your contact info
down right there. That's right.
Cool, cool, cool.
Hey, this is kind of like
Breakfast Club, huh?
- We are in a library.
- Yeah, I'm sure...
we've each got an issue balled up inside of us
that would make us cry if we talked about it.
Do you have something
balled up inside of you?
Well, I got a little doozy
in the chamber if things get emotional.
Hey, text message.
Let's give this bad boy a read.
- It's probably just for you.
- I've never gotten one of these.
They're-- It's probably-- You just--
"Say you have to pee.
I need to talk to you."
- "Say you have to pee."
- That is weird.
- "Say you have to pee. I need to--"
- Yeah, do you have to pee?
- No.
- Hmm.
- That's so weird.
- Well, I'm stumped. That's very creepy.
That makes two of us.
- What's that?
- Does it say you have to pee?
No, it's just someone with
a misguided grasp of abbreviation.
I just need five minutes, you guys,
so go ahead and study all the...
verbs... in Spanish.
- Abed?
- Yeah?
What's your read on that guy?
You look like Elisabeth Shue.
Just act natural.
Pretend you're watching
the athletic proceedings.
You couldn't stop me
from watching them.
There's a guy trying out for the track team
that is older than the game of poker.
He's kind of trucking.
Suppose I was to say to you it was
possible to get those test answers?
I would say, "go for that",
and could have said so in a text.
I'm asking you if you know the difference
between right and wrong.
I discovered at a very early age
that if I talk long enough...
I could make anything
right or wrong.
So either I'm God
or truth is relative.
- And in either case, Booyah.
- Oh, interesting.
It's just the average person has
a much harder time saying...
"Booyah", to moral relativism.
Duncan, you don't have to play shrink
to protect your pride.
I accept.
You're chicken.
Are you trying to use reverse psychology
on a psychologist?
No, I'm just using regular psychology
on a spineless, British twit.
I'm a professor!
You can't talk to me that way.
A six-year-old girl could talk
to you that way.
- Yes, because that would be adorable!
- No, because you're a five-year-old girl...
and there's a pecking order.
- Fine! I'll do it!
- Thank you.
Yeah, pleasure.
Bye!
Yes!
Good!
Why am I still shouting?
I'm drawing attention to myself.
You guys aren't gonna believe this,
but the rest of the group...
is here.
Are you the board-certified tutor?
That means you do my homework,
right, Seacrest?
I need to call my babysitter
if we're gon' be later than 10:00.
What board certifies a tutor?
- Where's Britta?
- Not sure.
But I invited more people
from Spanish class. Is that cool?
It's the coolest.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom...
and bring my jacket, wallet,
and keys with me...
in case there's a fire.
Should we go with him?
I'm leaving my homework
with Slumdog Millionaire over here.
That's borderline racist, I think.
And busted.
- Uh, listen.
- Now you know. I'm a smoker.
Yeah, but they're filtered,
so that makes them safe.
You ready to get started? Looks like
the rest of your group showed up.
Yeah, not mine, actually. I think
Abed took out a page on Craigslist.
And I was trained never
to say this...
but I think that group
may be untutorable.
Oh, really?
So why don't you and I go study over--
- Dinner?
- Or drinks.
I think, actually,
we should prioritize here...
and study first
and then go to dinner.
And if they really prove
to be untutorable...
we'll slip out early.
Oh... they will be...
untutorable.
All right.
Look at this crew.
All ready to study all night.
- Well, I can stay at least till 10:00.
- But who studies with strangers, right?
- My name is Jeff.
- Jeff, it's a pleasure.
My name is Pierce Hawthorne
and, yes...
That is Hawthorne as in Hawthorne Wipes,
the award-winning moist towellete.
I was just going to ask.
I'm also a toast master, so perhaps
I should do the introductions.
- Definitely!
- All right, you already know Brittles.
- Britta.
- Abed. Abed the Arab.
- Is that inappropriate?
- Sure.
Roy. Roy the wonder boy.
- Troy.
- Little Princess Elizabeth.
Annie.
And finally, this beautiful creature
is named Shirley.
Is that even close?
I'd like to know why I had to find out
about this group on accident?
This is getting way more
like Breakfast Club now.
- There's breakfast?
- Okay, um, maybe we should get started--
I've been a part of a lot of study groups,
that fell apart because of unresolved tension.
Shouldn't we address Annie's concern?
Did we not invite her?
Well, Annie, sweetie,
it's not behind your back.
Can we stop with the
"pumpkins" and the "sweeties"?
Being younger does
not make me inferior.
If anything, your age indicates
that you've made bad life decisions.
- Shirley has a response to that.
- No, no, no. I don't.
- You should. It looks like you do.
- Shirley, go ahead.
Okay, okay. Um...
I'm sure I've made
some bad life decisions...
and maybe Annie's decisions
will be better.
But I think she needs to decide whether
she wants to be considered a child...
or an adult, because children get pity
when not respected.
Adults, they get respect...
but they also get the back of they head grabbed
and their face pushed through jukeboxes.
Okay. Why don't we try learning
"jukebox" in Spanish?
- What are you doing?
- Pierce!
- Let's discuss this creepiness.
- Pardon you?
- What are you doing?
- I'm certified.
Are you unaware that Shirley
finds your advances inappropriate?
What advances?
You have been sexually harassing me
since the very first day of class.
Sexually harassing?
What?
That makes no sense to me.
Why would I harass somebody
who turns me on?
Saying she turns you on
is the harassment, dude.
Hey.
I am a prominent business leader
and a highly sought after dinner guest...
and I will not take courting advice
from some teenage boy.
Well, this teenage boy
is a quarterback and a prom king.
You're not prom king anymore, Troy.
This isn't Riverside High.
How'd you know I went there?
Because you're still wearing
your stupid letter jacket...
and more importantly,
I sat behind you in algebra.
Well, you're the girl that got
hooked on pills and then dropped out.
You're little Annie Adderall.
Yes, and you are a stupid jock...
who lost his scholarship by dislocating
both shoulders in a keg stand.
Keg flip.
They're very hard to pull off.
You don't know--
I'm a legend.
Would everybody just--
You know what I got for Christmas?
It was a banner year
at the Bender family.
I got a carton of cigarettes.
The old man grabbed me, he said,
"Hey, smoke up, Johnny!"
"No, dad! What about you?"
Well, uh...
that-- that actually was from
the Breakfast Club.
Nobody puts Baby in the corner.
Dirty dancing.
Hello?
It's professor Duncan.
Come to the parking lot now.
What's wrong with your voice?
I'm disguising it.
Uh, I'll be right back.
But while I'm gone, you guys need
to hash this stuff out.
No stone unturned.
Go!
What is he talking about?
Get in the car!
Act as if we've either just finished
or yet to begin driving.
Every answer to every test
in your curriculum this semester.
I knew you could do it, buddy.
Thank you.
Whoa there, grabby-grabby.
- What do I get?
- The satisfaction of being even.
Even, fairness, right, wrong.
There is no God. Booyah, Booyah.
What do you want from me?
Your Lexus.
My car for a semester's
worth of answers?
Will it be just
a semester though, Jeff?
Won't you be taking the easy way out
for the next four years?
I want payment in advance.
I want leather seats
with built-in ball warmers.
You know, bluffs this weak are how
your people lost the colonies.
Have a nice disbarment hearing.
What am I supposed to drive?
Why don't you take this car?
It's good for the earth.
Yeah, so is wiping your butt with a leaf,
but it's not how a man gets around!
- It is a disaster in there.
- Yeah, untutorable.
You like Thai food?
I love Thai food.
Wait, so this is a game to you?
You put human beings...
into a state of emotional shambles
for a shot at getting in my pants?
Why can't you see that
for the compliment that it is?
Okay, okay, okay. I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
I did a little bit of lying
to get close to you.
But how was I supposed to know
that you were smart and cool?
I mean, you look
like Elisabeth Shue.
- You're unbelievable.
- What do you want me to do?
Oh, maybe one decent thing could be
to go in there and clean up your mess.
Okay, I am the Barack Obama
of this room.
Okay, if I do that,
then dinner, right?
I'm here to learn Spanish!
I got children at home!
Yeah, fine, whatever.
As if there's a dinner on earth
that could make me forget...
you are a shallow douchebag.
Oh, you're gonna eat those words
when you see my new car.
All right, everybody!
I want to say something.
Sit down.
You don't have to yell.
I don't appreciate your tone.
You know what makes humans
different from other animals?
Feet.
No, no, no. Come on.
Bears have feet.
We're the only species on earth
that observes Shark Week.
Sharks don't even observe
Shark Week, but we do.
For the same reason
I can pick up this pencil...
tell you it's name is Steve,
and go like this.
And part of you dies
just a little bit on the inside...
because people can connect
with anything.
We can sympathize with a pencil.
We can forgive a shark.
And we can give Ben Affleck
an Academy Award for screenwriting.
- Big mistake.
- He's got a point.
People can find the good in just
about anything but themselves.
Look at me. It's clear to all of you
that I am awesome...
but I can never admit that,
because that would make me an ass.
But what I can do is see
what makes Annie awesome.
She's driven.
We need driven people...
or the lights go out
and the ice cream melts.
And Pierce.
We need guys like Pierce.
This guy has wisdom to offer.
- The Dalai Lama and I--
- We should listen to him sometime.
We wouldn't regret it.
And Shirley.
Shirley has earned our respect,
not as a wife, not as a mother...
but as a woman.
And don't test her on that,
because that thing about the jukebox...
was way too specific
to be improvised.
And Troy.
Who cares if Troy thinks
he's all that?
Maybe he is.
You think astronauts go to the moon
because they hate oxygen?
No, they're trying to impress
their high school's prom king.
And Abed.
Abed's a shaman.
You ask him to pass the salt...
he gives you a bowl of soup,
because you know what?
Soup is better.
Abed is better.
You are all better
than you think you are.
You are just designed not to believe it
when you hear it from yourself.
Soup?
I want you to look
to the person to your left.
Sorry. Look at the person
sitting next to you.
Look at her?
Okay.
- This?
- Yeah.
I want you to extend
to that person...
the same compassion that you extend
to sharks, pencils, and Ben Affleck.
I want you to say to that person,
"I forgive you."
- I forgive you.
- You little twerp.
Pierce, I'd like you to say,
"I forgive you."
He didn't say it?
You've just stopped being
a study group.
You have become something
unstoppable.
I hereby pronounce you a community.
Oh, that's nice.
I like that.
This isn't like Breakfast Club anymore.
Now it's like Stripes or Meatballs.
Anything with Bill Murray, really.
I agree with Abed that tonight
has been very special.
And now, if you'll excuse me...
I have a dinner engagement
with Britta.
- Britta?
- I lied.
Thanks for calming everyone down.
But since you're not a Spanish tutor...
just a lying creep
who purposely upset everyone...
in an attempt to get with me,
I'd appreciate it if you left...
and stopped wasting all of our time.
Everybody ready?
Fine.
And I'm happy to report...
that one of the benefits
of being a lying creep...
is having all the answers
to tomorrow's test.
And I'm happy
to share them with anyone...
whose time I've wasted more
than they've wasted mine.
Uh, Jeff, if you have
all the answers...
why the hell did you start
this study group?
I don't have a study group, Pierce.
I made it up.
- What about the "look left" speech?
- Made it up. That's what I do.
I make things up
and I got paid a lot of money...
to do it before I came
to this school-shaped toilet.
- I was a lawyer.
- Oh, God.
That explains everything.
You know, I thought you were like
Bill Murray in any of his films...
but you're more like Michael Douglas
in any of his films.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, you have Asperger's.
"Ass burger."
- It's a serious disorder.
- It really is.
If it's so serious,
why don't they call it meningitis?
Yeah.
- "Ass burger."
- Burger for your ass.
Jeffrey, before you say anything you may want
to think about the gift you've been given.
- An excuse to punch a hippy?
- No. No, not that.
An important lesson, my friend.
You see, the tools you acquired
to survive out there...
will not help you here at Greendale.
What you have, my friend,
is a second chance at an honest life.
Why are people trying
to teach me things...
at a school that has
an express tuition aisle?
Give me my keys.
No, I have to keep the car
for the lesson-- the less--
Don't hit me.
Please, don't hit me.
Jeffrey?
Jeffrey, are we cool?
Are we cool?
We cool.
I like you, Jeffrey.
You remind me of myself
at your age.
I deserve that.
You know...
I've been divorced... seven times.
Sometimes I think
I'm doing something wrong.
You keep getting married.
I never looked at it that way.
Shouldn't you guys be studying?
Yeah, things got kind
of boring after you left.
Let me ask you something.
People been clowning me about
this jacket since I got here, but...
if I take it off to make them happy,
that just makes me weak, right?
Listen.
It doesn't matter.
You lose the jacket to please them.
You keep it to piss them off.
Either way, it's for them.
That's what's weak.
Wow.
You just wrinkled my brain, man.
- He's good, isn't he?
- He's real good.
Shouldn't you be rolling around
on a bed covered in test answers?
I don't have any of the answers.
I'm gonna--
I'm gonna flunk the test.
You just, like, study for, like, an hour.
It's not that hard.
You seem pretty smart.
You got a sports coat.
Well, me.
Funny thing about being smart
is that you can get through most of life...
without ever having
to do any work.
So, uh...
I'm not really sure how to do that.
What's going on?
Can you guys hear me?
Am I deaf?
- Can you hear me talking right now? Yes?
- Yes.
That's good.
You know what?
Jeff, actually,
we didn't get that far without you...
so if you want
to come back upstairs--
Really?
Well, it is your study group, so.
- Come on, let's study.
- Sounds good.
No pressure.
I'm sorry I called you Michael Douglas
and I see your value now.
Well, that's the nicest
thing anyone's ever said to me.
www.tvsubtitles.net